what you're saying, they think it means apocalypse.
No.
You know, they think it means, well, do you know how to fish?
I hear them all the time.
Y'all don't even know how to fish.
However, what you're saying and what Palestinians
continue to show us is that we are so,
we, we, ooh, about to kill it.
We are heirloom seeds.
Mm-hmm.
He's our seeds that have been through it.
So they have learned how to grow through several seasons,
and they have remembered the hardships and the goodships
in order to grow even stronger and sturdier
and more bountiful and more flavorful.
Our ancestors are within us.
We've been here before.
We are heirloom seeds.
And so when we talk about a new beginning,
it's not one that we have to craft from nothing.
It's one that we just have to remember without the function.
Mm.
Yes.
Thank you.
Wow.